Jason Klotz

Front-End Web Developer



3131 Lantana Ct.
Palmdale, CA 93551
(661)208-9057
jason.klotz5@gmail.com

WHY I WANT TO BE HERE

I have become familiar with Lemonade Stand through a friend and current employee, and have seen how the company and it's culture has positively impacted his life. Lemonade Stand's view on improving the digital marketing landscape by making the experience as enjoyable for the client as possible is very encouraging. The positive values that the company tries to instill in its employees really make it seem like a great place to get rooted and invested in. I would be very interested in using my skill set as web developer to benefit the Lemonade Stand team.

HOW CAN I ADD VALUE

I have spent the past year training under a few web developers becoming proficient in both HTML and CSS, as well as becoming knowledgeable in Javascript and Wordpress. I also have an understanding of the main principles behind the ADA guidelines and DNS records. I have a passion for technology and more importantly, creating great looking and functional websites. I'm a quick learner, a hard worker, and I'm very excited to improve my skills as a Web Developer in any ways I can.

WHO I KNOW

Jared Briones, SEO Specialist - (661) 860-9518

Joseph Moore, Senior Product Developer at Scorpion - (661) 231-5886 joseph.moore@scorpion.co

Melanie Casillas, Freelance Character Designer-(818) 957-2829

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Web Developer — *Freelance*

April 2022 - August 2022

Used HTML,CSS, and Javascript to create a custom framework, designed a new website layout, transferred all relevant images and text from an old website, made the website responsive, abided by basic ADA guidelines, and transferred website hosting platform.

Computer System Integrator — *Freelance*

September 2019 - Current

Find computer use cases from clients, create computer parts list, assemble system (including updating bios if necessary and installing operating system), and troubleshooting any potential problems.

UPS — Personal Vehicle Driver

October 2021 - December 2021

Contributed to organizing packages for team's routes, Worked independently to deliver packages to 100-140 homes per day while finding the most efficient route.

WEB DEVELOPMENT SKILLS AND CERTIFICATIONS

HTML, CSS, and Javascript-

Learned how to systematically code a CSS framework, write semantically correct HTML, accurately recreate designs with HTML and CSS, and knowledge of Javascript principles and use cases.

Sololearn HTML Certification

Sololearn CSS Certification

Sololearn Javascript Certification

Wordpress

MS Office Products

EDUCATION

California State University-Northridge, Northridge, CA

September 2020 - May 2021

Completed 19 credits toward a B.Sc. in Nutrition and Dietetics

Antelope Valley College, Lancaster, CA

January 2017 - May 2020

Completed 81 credits toward a B.Sc. in Nutrition and Dietetics

Highland High School, Palmdale, CA

High School Diploma

Graduated May 2016